（逢）塚原先輩
もう一本　お願いします
Tsukahara-senpai.
Time me again, please.
（響）ええ　いいわよ　七咲
Okay.
Go ahead, Nanasaki.
〈（純一）う～ん　本当だ
七咲が言ってたとおり〉
She's right.
Cream Oobanyaki are pretty tasty, just like Nanasaki said.
〈大判焼きのクリームも
結構おいしいな〉
チョット　イイデスカ？
Do you have a moment?
わあッ
コワガラナクテ　イイヨ
No need to be frightened.
コレ　アゲル
These are for you.
タノシイ　ユウエンチネ
ミンナデ　キテネ
It's a fun amusement park.
Bring everyone along!
T-Thank you...
サッ　サンキュー　あれ？
Huh?
Young ladies, do you like amusement parks?
オジョサ～ン
ユウエンチハ　オスキデスカ→
We're opening soon.
コンド　オープンシマス
ゼヒゼヒ　キテクダサイ→
Don't forget to come!
A wonderful amusement park is opening soon!
ステキナ　ユウエンチ
オープンデス
Have you started preparing for the finals?
（部員Ａ）期末の準備してる？
（部員Ｂ）してる　してる
Yep, I have.
（部員Ｃ）ええッ　ウソ？
ウソ～
Really?
Just kidding.
Come on!
なんだ～
（部員Ｄ）ホッとしちゃダメでしょ
You shouldn't take it so lightly.
塚原先輩　お先に失礼します
Tsukahara-senpai, I'm going home.
お疲れさま
See you.
Butterfly
3rd year     Tatamino   Miku
2nd year     Kichida    Yuka
Backstroke
3rd year      Mita     Kanami
2nd year     Kawagami    Yui
Umeda      Takaka
What am I gonna do about this?
〈どうしようかしらね〉
・～
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaetara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたら
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
SS
Nando mo kisetsu wo kasaneta ne ano hi kara
The seasons have come and gone since that day
何度も季節を重ねたね　あの日から
Kyou made doumo arigatou
And even today, I remain so grateful
今日までどうもありがとう
Semai rojiura mezashi
We head towards a narrow back alley
狭い路地裏目指し
Shiroi iki ga odoru
As our white breaths dance in the air
白い息が踊る
Itai kurai nigitta te wo hiite
You hold me by the hand so hard it almost hurts
痛いくらい握った手をひいて
Kimi wa susunde yuku
And pull me with you as you walk on forward
君は進んでいく
Ima sugu kisu shitakatta
I wanted to kiss you right then
今すぐキスしたかった
Kakureta jihanki no ura
Hidden behind the vending machines
隠れた自販機の裏
Hanikande mitsumeatta
We shyly gazed at each other
ハニかんで見つめあった
Yasashii kimochi afureta
And I was overcome with kind feelings for you
優しいキモチ溢れた
Kimi wa kimi no mama de
You just being you
君は君のままで
Boku wa boku no mama de
And me just being me
僕は僕のままで
Subete wakariaeta nara
If we could understand each other completely
全て分かり合えたなら
Futari wa hitotsu da yo
The two of us would become one
２人は１つだよ
Donna chiisa na shiawase mo
No matter how small it may be
どんな小さな幸せも
Mitsukedaseru ki ga suru yo
We'll surely find happiness
見つけ出せる気がするよ
Yasashiku nareta no wa kimi no okage
I learned to be kind because of you
優しくなれたのは　君のおかげ
Senpai.
先輩
Sorry I kept you waiting.
お待たせしました
ああ　ううん　全然待ってないよ
Nah, I didn't wait at all.
僕も今　来たところ
そうですか
I just got here myself.
Really?
今日は　いい天気になって
よかったね
I'm glad it's so nice out today.
Yes.
そうですね
あれ？
Huh?
By the way, where's Ikuo-kun?
そういえば郁夫君はどうしたの？
あの～　カゼです
カゼ？
Um...
He's ill.
He's ill?
I guess he kicked his blanket off last night while he was asleep.
ゆうべ　寝ているときに
布団をけとばしたみたいで
その…
So...
《この前言ってた弟君と
３人で一緒にとか…》
You mentioned your little brother recently,
so I thought the three of us could go together...
Well?
《どうかな？》
《３人で…　ですか？》
The three of us?
《うん》
《遊園地…》
Yeah.
An amusement park...
《分かりました
じゃあ郁夫にも話してみますね》
Okay.
I'll talk to Ikuo about it.
《ああ》
Mom will be at home to watch him today, so I'm sure he'll be fine.
でも今日は
母が家でみてくれているので
大丈夫だと思います
そっか　それならよかった
I see.
That's a relief.
ああッ　じゃあ今日は２人っきりか
So it's just the two of us?
そうなりますね
I guess so.
嫌なんですか？
You don't like it?
That's not true!  At all!
嫌なんかじゃないよ！　全然
行きましょう　先輩
Let's go, Senpai.
せっかくの遊園地なんですから
思いっきり楽しまないと
It is an amusement park, after all.
We need to have as much fun as we can!
You're right.
そうだね　じゃあ　行こうか
Okay, let's go!
あの～　先輩
えッ　何？
Um, Senpai?
What?
今日の私の服に
何かコメントとかないんですか
Don't you have anything to say about my outfit?
ああ　ごめん　よく似合ってるよ
Nanasaki Ai Arc
Chapter 3
Transformation
I'm sorry.  You look really nice.
Too late.
遅すぎます
ごめん
Sorry.
（笑う逢）
（客達）うわ～ッ！
（客達）キャ～ッ！
大丈夫ですか？　先輩
Are you okay, Senpai?
ジェットコースターのスピードは
平気なんだけど
I don't mind the speed of roller coasters, but the height...
高さがね…
そうなんですか
I see...
じゃあ　次は
あれに乗ってみません？
Well then, why don't we ride that next?
・（美也）お兄ちゃんてば
ひどいよね→
Onii-chan's such a jerk.
美也を置いて
遊園地に行っちゃうんだから→
He left me behind and went to an amusement park.
こうなったらお兄ちゃんに
負けないくらい遊んでやろうね
In that case, we've gotta have just as much fun as him!
ねッ　紗江ちゃん
（紗江）うん　でも　どこへ行くの？
Right, Sae-chan?
Yes, but where will we go?
それがまだ決まってないんだよね
I dunno yet.
（梨穂子）あれ～　美也ちゃん
Oh?  Miya-chan!
・（美也）りほちゃん
お友達？
Riho-chan!
Is she your friend?
Yeah.  She's my classmate, Nakata Sae-chan.
うん　同じクラスの中多紗江ちゃん
And she's a childhood friend of mine, Riho-chan.
で　幼なじみの　りほちゃん
ウチの学校の２年生なんだよ
She's a junior in our school.
N-Nice to meet you.  I'm Nakata Sae.
はじめまして　中多紗江です
こんにちは　桜井梨穂子です
Good afternoon.  I'm Sakurai Rihoko.
Riho-chan, what are you up to?
・（美也）今日はどうしたの？
ほら　もうすぐ創設祭でしょ？
Well, isn't the Founder's Festival coming up soon?
そのときに出す
お茶請けの研究も兼ねて
I'm doing research on the sweets we'll be serving with the tea.
最近　この辺りにできたっていう
和菓子屋さんに行くの
So I'm going to a Japanese candy store that was recently built here.
とってもおいしくて
行列ができるくらいなんだって
I hear their stuff is so good that people line up for them.
へえ～　すごい
美也ちゃん達は？
Wow, amazing!
What about you guys?
Well, we're still figuring out where to go.
それがね
まだ行き先が決まってなくて
じゃあ　一緒に行く？
えッ　いいの？
Wanna come with me?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
うん　どんなお菓子が
おいしかったか
You guys can help me figure out which sweets are the best.
教えてもらえると参考になるし
行く行く　いいよね？　紗江ちゃん
We'll definitely go!
Sae-chan, you don't mind, right?
うん　楽しそう
Sure, it sounds like fun.
All right!  It's decided!
よ～し　決定！
行こ行こ　りほちゃん→
Let's go, Riho-chan!
和菓子　和菓子～
Candy, candy!
「ファラオ謎の入り口」？
Pharaoh's Riddle Entrance?
ホラーハウスみたいだけど
It looks like a haunted house...
Phar
aoh's
Rid
dle
En
t
r
an
c
e
Phar
aoh's
Rid
dle
En
t
r
an
c
e
入ってみる？
いいですね
Wanna go in?
Okay.
おもしろそうです
It looks interesting.
（２人）あッ！
It's pretty dark in here.
中は結構　暗いんだな
先輩　足元には
気をつけてくださいね
Senpai, watch your step, okay?
うん
Yeah.
ウオオ～ッ！
キャ～ッ！
やっぱり　きたか
えッ？
There it is.
そろそろ来る頃じゃないかとは
思ってたんだ
I was wondering when something like this was gonna show up.
Take a closer look, Nanasaki.
ほら　七咲　よく見てみなよ
It's really well-made, but it's just a fake.
よくできてるとは思うけど
ただの作り物だよ
Senpai, are you good with scary stuff?
先輩　こういうの強いんですか？
う～ん　さすがに
得意ってほどじゃないけど
I wouldn't say I'm good with it, but I'm not bad with it either.
苦手ではないかな
そうなんですか
I see...
さッ　先に進もう
はい
Well, let's keep going.
Okay...
Man, that scared me.
〈ああ　ビックリした〉
I'm glad I was more than prepared for that.
〈必要以上に
警戒しててよかったよ〉
I can't let myself scream in front of Nanasaki.
〈七咲の前で悲鳴なんて
あげるわけにはいかないもんな〉
・（恵子）薫　カッコいい～
Kaoru, you're so cool.
Really?  Am I really that handsome?
・（薫）そう？
そんなに　あたしイケてる？
（恵子）イケてる　イケてる
もし告白されたら
You are, you are!
I'd say okay right away if you confessed to me!
私　即ＯＫしちゃうよ
"Keiko, you won't be getting any sleep tonight."
・（薫）「恵子　今夜は寝かせないぜ」
みたいな？
Something like that?
・（恵子）ステキ～
You're so cool!
どうしたんですか？　先輩
What's the matter, Senpai?
Nah, it's nothing...
ううん　何でもない
Am I just imagining things?
気のせいだったのかな？
どうしたの　君？　泣いてるの？
What's going on?  Are you crying?
Huh?  Ayatsuji-san?
えッ　絢辻さん？
（幼い詞）
うふふ　うふふふ　はははッ
先輩？
Senpai?
何だろ　疲れてるのかな
What was that?
Maybe I'm just tired.
We've come to a really large room.
何だか広い場所に出たな
そうですね
You're right.
何だ？
地震？
What?!
An earthquake?!
キャ～ッ！
うわあああ
我の眠りを妨げる者よ
You have disturbed my rest!
千年王国の呪いを受けるがよい！
Prepare to receive the curse of an ancient kingdom!
This must be the main attraction...
これってアトラクションだよね？
すごい迫力だけど
先輩ッ
It's pretty intense.
Senpai!
ざれ言などいらぬ　覚悟を決めろ！
I have no need for your idle banter.
Prepare yourself!
覚悟？
Prepare myself?
ウオオオ～ッ！
（２人）うわ～ッ！
止まってる？
Did it stop?
Huh?  Nanasaki?
あれ　七咲？
Nanasaki?!
七咲？
先輩
Senpai.
ああッ
Here.  I'm right here.
ここです　私はここにいます
まさかと思うけど
この味噌ラーメンが七咲なのか？
I can't believe I'm asking this...
But is that Miso Ramen you, Nanasaki?
はい？　先輩　何を言って…
Huh?  Senpai, what are you talking about?
いや　でもさ…
But look...
そう言われると
何だか自分でも　そんな気が…
Now that you mention it, I get the feeling you're right...
I'm... Miso Ramen?
私が味噌ラーメンだなんて
あの　もしもし？
Um, hello?
どういう仕掛けなのかは
知りませんけど
I don't know what kind of trick this is,
but could you please turn Nanasaki back-
できれば早く七咲を元に…
うわ～ッ！
先輩　大丈夫ですか？
Senpai!  Are you okay?!
先輩　先輩！
Senpai!  Senpai!
よかった　無事だったんですね
What a relief.  You're all right.
先輩？
Senpai?
Ishikawa Butter
七咲
はい　何ですか？
Nanasaki.
Yes, what is it?
Nanasaki, you smell really delicious.
七咲って　すごくおいしそうな
においがするよね
Huh?
はあ？
I get the feeling Miso Ramen is best with melted butter.
特にバターの溶けた
味噌ラーメンって
最高な気がするんだ
先輩？　冗談ですよね
S-Senpai?  You're joking, right?
そんなことより
早く元に戻してください
More importantly, please get me back to normal!
I'll go stale if you don't hurry!
じゃないと私　伸びちゃいます
バターが…
The butter is...
うわあ～ッ！
Your finger...
指　先輩の親指が…
Senpai, your thumb is...
Your breath is...
息が…
Senpai, you're going to...
私　先輩に…
フーッ
食べられちゃう
...eat me...
七咲…
Nanasaki?
うわッ　ごめん！
S-Sorry!
Um... for a while it was like I wasn't myself or something...
その…　一瞬自分じゃ
なかったみたいっていうか
Um, I'm really sorry.
その…　本当にごめん
もう知りません
I don't care anymore.
おかしいな
どうしちゃってたんだろう　僕…
That was weird.  What on Earth was wrong with me?
はい　これあったかいよ
Here.
It's nice and warm.
お礼は言いませんよ
I'm not going to thank you.
分かってる　これはお詫びだよ
I know.
This is an apology.
I'm really sorry.
本当にごめん
You were trying to eat me.
私のこと食べようとするなんて
だから　ごめんって
I said I'm sorry.
（笑う逢）
えッ　何？
いえ
What?
Well, it was pretty amusing now that I think about it.
今　思い返すと
おもしろかったなって
R-Really?
そッ　そう？
Actually... my times haven't been improving during practice.
実は私　最近部活で
タイムが伸びなくて
I was a little stressed because of that.
少し　ストレスがたまってたんです
でもスッキリしました
そっか
But I feel much better now.
Really?
Does that mean I helped you out a bit?
それはお役に立てたのかな？
Yes.  So I guess I'll forgive you.
はい　だから許してあげます
ありがとう
Thanks.
Senpai.
先輩
うん？
覚えてますか？
えッ？
Do you remember?
This park is where I first met you.
この公園　私が先輩と
初めて会った所です
ああ　そういえば
僕と梅原が公園に入ってきて
Ah, now that you mention it...
Umehara and I showed up here,
and you were on the swings.  Then...
七咲がブランコに乗ってて
それで…
先輩が
チカンしようとしたんですよね
You tried to peek up my skirt.
That's not right at all!
違うよ　あれは…
分かってます
I know.
先輩
Senpai.
一緒にブランコに乗りませんか？
Why don't we ride the swings together?
Are you sure you want to ride it like this?
本当にこれで乗るの？
はい
でも　これって…
Yes.
But isn't this kinda...
ほら先輩　いきますよ
うわあッ
Come on, Senpai!
Here we go!
まだ動いたばかりですよ
でも…
We're just getting started.
But...
もっともっと　いきますからね
We're gonna go even higher!
うわあ
そ～れッ
うわあッ
There!
Senpai?  How is it?
先輩　どうですか？
ああッ　うん…
Doesn't this feel great?
気持ちいいですよね
先輩　どこ見てるんですか？
Senpai, where do you think you're looking?
えッ　どこって…　あはははッ
Uh... where, you ask?
ほいッ
Careful, we're still swinging!
動いてるのに危ない
おしおきです
This is punishment.
おしおきって
Punishment?
This way, you can't look up my skirt anymore.
この格好なら　もうスカートの中は
のぞけませんよね
That's true, but...
それは　そうだけど…
七咲
Nanasaki...
本当にエッチな先輩ですよね
You really are perverted, Senpai.
〈まさかキスだなんて〉
I didn't think she'd kiss me.
〈もしかして七咲は僕のこと…〉
Does this mean Nanasaki's interested in...
In that case, I...
〈だとしたら僕は…〉
（梅原）よお　大将どうした？
Yo.
Sup, boss?
めちゃめちゃ
テンション低いじゃねえか
You look pretty down today.
あれか　寝不足か？
Are you getting enough sleep?
ちゃんと米　食ってるか？
Are you eating properly?
You'll definitely cheer up right away after you see this though.
だが　これを見れば一発で
元気になること間違いなしよ
Wanna see?  I'm sure you do.
見たいか？　見たいよな～
しょうがねえ　少しだけだぞ→
Fine, just a little.
ほら　これが前に話してた
兄貴の秘蔵本だ
Look, it's my brother's secret porn mag I've been talking about.
借りるのに苦労したんだぜ～
Borrowing it was really tough, man.
おっと　今は　まだ見せられねえな
Whoa, I can't let you see it now though.
Guys need to hold back from time to time.
男には我慢するときも必要なんだ
というか　その方があとの楽しみが
何倍にも…
That way, the pleasure you get afterwards is magnified...
て　おい　無視か？
無視かよ　橘　おーい！
Wait, you're ignoring me?
Are you ignoring me, Tachibana?
Hey!
あッ
Good afternoon, Senpai.
こんにちは　先輩
G-Good afternoon, Nanasaki.
こッ　こんにちは　七咲
What's the matter?
どうしたんですか？
顔が赤いですよ
Your face is really red.
熱でもあるんですか？
Do you have a fever?
平気　大丈夫　何でもない
I'm good, I'm fine.  It's nothing.
うん？
Oh?
Huh?  Nanasaki's no different from usual.
〈あれ？　七咲は普通だ〉
Am I caring too much about this?
〈僕が意識しすぎなだけ？〉
Senpai?
先輩？
あのさ　七咲
Hey, Nanasaki.
はい
昨日のことなんだけど
Yes.
About what happened yesterday...
その…　公園で
Um... at the park-
Senpai.
先輩
何？
What is it?
Um... they're doing special offers at the store today,
あの　今日も特売があるんですけど
so could you come with me again?
また　つきあってもらえますか？
えッ？　ああ　うん
よかった
Huh?
Yeah, okay.
Yay.
では　すみませんけど
部活が終わるまで
Then... I'm sorry, but could you wait for me on the grounds somewhere until practice is over?
中庭かどこかで
待っていてもらえますか？
うん　分かった
Yeah, okay.
七咲　遅いな
Nanasaki's late.
I wonder if practice ended already.
まだ部活終わらないのかな
Huh?
あれ？
Um... you're all in the swim team, right?
あの　水泳部の人ですよね
そうですけど
ああ　この人　この前の
We are.
Ah, he's the guy who...
あ～あ～
もう部活って終わったんですか？
Has practice ended?
ええ　終わりましたけど
七咲ですか？
Yes, it ended.
Looking for Nanasaki?
Y-Yes, well...
ええ　まあ…
（笑う部員達）
Nanasaki was talking to Tsukahara-senpai when I last saw her.
七咲なら
塚原先輩と話してましたよ
I think she's still at the pool.
まだプールだと思います
T-Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
ヒューヒューッ
やる～ッ
Whoo, whoo!
Go for it!
〈部活が終わっているなら
プールに行っても平気だよな〉
Since practice's over, going to the pool should be fine.
Excuse me!
失礼しまーす
うん？
What's the matter, Nanasaki?
どうしたんだ？　七咲
Nanasaki, wait!
七咲　待ちなさい
Tsukahara-senpai, what on Earth-
塚原先輩　一体何が？
ごめんなさい
今は　それどころじゃないの
I'm sorry, now's not the time.
Nanasaki.
七咲
Nanasaki!
七咲！
ああッ
I love you feeling baby my heart
七咲！
Nanasaki!
I love you need you baby
Your voice in my heart
Don't you like being alone with me?
Watashi to futari iya desu ka
私と二人嫌ですか？
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Nanika iu koto nai desu ka
何か言う事無いですか？
As you touched the tip of my finger in the dark
Kurayami no naka fureta yubisaki
暗闇の中　触れた指先
七咲！
Nanasaki!
Happy and embarrassed, I said "I don't care anymore!"
Ureshi hazukashi "mou shirimasen"
嬉し恥ずかし　「もう知りません」
In the park where we first met
Hajimete no kouen
初めての公園
On the swing of our memories
Omoide no buranko
思い出のブランコ
Where do you think you're looking?
Doko wo mite iru n desu ka
どこを見ているんですか？
You haven't changed one bit
Aikawarazu desu ne
相変わらずですね
Close enough to feel your heart beating, I said
Kodou sae todoku kyori
鼓動さえ届く距離
（号泣する逢）
"This is punishment!"
"Oshioki desu"
「お仕置きです」
The water surface envelops my love for you
Koigokoro tsutsumikomu minamo
恋心　包み込む （水面） みなも
そっか　そうだったんだ
I see.  So that's why.
Yes.
はい　塚原先輩から　今度の大会
Tsukahara-senpai told me one of the juniors was selected as the backstroker for the swim meet this year.
背泳の選手は　２年生の先輩を
エントリーすると言われて
But Nanasaki, you were occupied with the math makeup, your brother, and all sorts of things...
でも　最近　七咲は
数学の追試とか　弟のこととか
いろいろあったから
いいんです
It's okay.
そういうのとは関係なく
That has nothing to do with it.
Even I know that I'm having trouble improving my time.
タイムが伸び悩んでいたことは
自分でも分かっていましたから
But I still have another two years, so I won't give up.
でも　私には　あと
２年間ありますから頑張ります
そっか　応援するよ
I see.  I'll be rooting for you.
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
あのさ
You know...
こういうこと聞いていいのか
どうか分からないけど
I dunno if I should be asking this, but...
Yes?
はい？
どうして　あのとき逃げ出したの？
Why did you take off back then?
私　塚原先輩に泣いてるところを
見られたくなくて
I... didn't want Tsukahara-senpai to see me cry...
So that's why you took off.
だから逃げ出したのか
はい
Yes.
But Tachibana-senpai, I wanted you to see it even less.
でも　橘先輩には
もっと見られたくなかったんです
えッ
ごめん
いえ　すみません
Sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
そういう意味じゃないんですけど
That's not what I meant...
嬉しかったよ
えッ？
I was happy.
Huh?
僕は嬉しかった
I was happy.
いつもと違う七咲が見られて
It made me happy to see a different side of you, Nanasaki.
なんか嬉しかったよ
先輩は…
えッ？
Senpai...
どうして私のことを　その…
Why did you... uh... chase after me?
追いかけてきてくれたんですか？
I actually don't really know.
実は僕にもよく分からないんだ
えッ？
でも　泣いている七咲を見たら
Huh?
But when I saw you cry, before I knew it,
I started chasing after you with all my might.
何だか知らないうちに
無我夢中で追いかけてた
そうですか
うん
Really...
Yeah.
ああッ　特売
Oh yeah, the special offers-
もう　この時間だと
間に合わないですよ
There's no way we'll make it now.
You're right.
そうだね
すみません　私がお願いしたのに
Sorry, I was the one who asked...
ううん　いいよ　気にしないで
はい
Nah, it's fine.  Don't worry about it.
Okay.
では　私はこっちなので
Well, I'm going this way...
うん　じゃあ
あの　先輩
Yeah.  See you.
Um, Senpai...
うん？
Are you free now?
これから時間　空いてますか？
えッ　これから？
Huh?  Now?
いえ　すみません　何でもないです
Nah, I'm sorry.  It's nothing.
それより先輩　クリスマスに
何か予定ありますか？
By the way, Senpai.
Do you have any plans for Christmas?
クリスマス？
ううん　特にはないけど
Christmas?
No, nothing in particular.
Well, our Swim Club is doing an Oden food cart.
あの　水泳部で
おでんの屋台をやるんです
もし　よかったら
手伝ってもらえませんか？
Would you like to help?
いろいろ
力仕事もあるみたいなので
It looks like there'll be a lot of muscle work,
先輩にいてもらえると
すごく助かります
so it'd be great if you could be there.
う～ん　水泳部の人達には
迷惑かけちゃってるもんな
Hmm, I do owe the Swim Club for all the trouble I've caused.
うん　いいよ
Yeah, sure.
Well then, I'm counting on you.
じゃあ　よろしくお願いします
Yurayura yureteru Surface Of The Pool
The surface of the pool shakes and sways
ゆらゆら　揺れてる
・～
Takaku tobikomu kakikomu
I dive in and it carries me under
高く　飛び込む　掻き込む
Watashi tsutsunde
It envelops me
私　包んで
Kokoro no okusoko he michiteku
And fills the depths of my heart
心の奥底へ　満ちてく
Nani shiteru n desu ka
What are you doing?
何してるんですか
Nani wo mite iru n desu ka
What are you looking at?
何を見ているんですか
Toikaketeru n desu
I'm asking you a question
問い掛けてるんです
Poker Face
ポーカーフェース
Childlike
Mitai kawaii awai kitai
I want to see it, it's cute, it's fleeting, the expectation
見たい　可愛い　淡い　期待
Tanoshii desu
It's all fun
楽しいです
Majime sugata fui ni miserare
When I unexpectedly saw your serious side
マジメ姿　不意に見せられ
Mune no oku ga tsukiugoite
Something stirred deep within my chest
胸の奥が突き動いて
Kokoro yurayura yureteru Feel Comfortable
The swaying and shaking of my heart feels comfortable
心　ゆらゆら　揺れてる
Takaku habataku koeteku
I'll flap my wings and fly over
高く　羽ばたく　越えてく
Ashita aeru
So I can see you tomorrow
明日会える
Utakata uiteru koi moyou
Patterns of love bubble on the water surface
泡沫　浮いてる　恋模様
Konna kanjou nan da to omoimasu ka
What do you think these feelings are?
こんな感情　何だと思いますか
Tawai mo naku soba de
I want to be by your side
たわいもなく傍で
Waraiaitai desu
And laugh with you without a care in the world
笑い合いたいです
Watashi no kimochi nandesu
These are my feelings
私の気持ちなんです
To You Innocent
Preview
Next episode preview.
So she's having trouble improving her time, huh?
I wonder if she can improve her time once she gets over this.
Yeah.
I'm sure Ai-chan'll become a really fast swimmer.
Morishima-senpai?
Ah, you're always peeking at the Swim Club, right?
That's right.
I'm always peeking in secret, since Hibiki gets mad at me whenever she finds out.
Next episode: "Confession".
Next Episode
Confession
Ai-chan's armpits are pretty sexy
when she's swimming the backstroke.
A-Armpits?